{
    "id": "943a47218d9c4885ba30bca232a3eb29",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I don’t think I …………………. be able to come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… not come unless he is invited.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… be punctual.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ought",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. I help you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… you mind moving a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that I ……………… visit his home whenever I wanted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "could",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ………………. see her, give her my love.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. you like another cup of coffee?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Could",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ……………… not drive so fast.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you ………………… stop lying",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}